betjm.com 2006-06-17

# Bet Jamaica - The Player's Paradise

**Privacy Policy**  
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Bet Jamaica, Ltd. . We are based in Jamaica. Our principal activity is: Sports information and wagering. Our privacy policy covers Bet Jamaica, Ltd. and its Web sites.

BETJAMAICA  
#1 Mangrove Way  
MBFZ Freeport  
Montego Bay, Jamaica.  
Direct/Local: 1-876-979-8565

TOLL FREE NUMBERS  
Phone: 1-800-329-2909  
Fax: 1-800-329-4156  
Dialing from Canada: 1-888-405-4637

Web Site: http://www.betjamaica.com

Your privacy rights are important to us. To allow you to make an informed decision concerning your privacy, we are providing this notice as a means of explaining our online information practices and any choices you can make about the way your information is collected and handled. 

**You Are Giving Your Consent**  
By accessing our site, you consent to our right to collect and use the information described in this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page. 

**It's About You**  
We may collect personally identifiable information about you. For most persons accessing our site, this information concerns basic, non-personally identifiable information, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Opera), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP, Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., MSN, Earthlink). This information is collected in greater detail if you join our site as a Member, and in most parts of most of our sites, only Members will be able to order programs and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings. Information collected from our Members may include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about our Members interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

 **How We Use Your Information**  
Personally identifiable information submitted by our Members is stored in our Members' database and is used to fulfill your requests for services, programs and, from time to time, any products we may offer. We routinely provide this information to third-party credit card processors which assist us in charging our Members for their orders. Some or all of this information may also be transmitted to outside sources whom we engage for the express purpose of assisting us in the verification of such credit card information and the weeding out of fraudulent data.

Data received from casual visitors, who have not yet decided to become Members, is stored in log files located on our servers and is now in the process of becoming part of an overall database which includes information received from visitors and Members, alike. 

Occasionally, we receive special information from non-Members, such as requests from those persons who are interested in receiving daily e-mails containing special communications, such as solicitations and other offers. This information may be kept in our own databases or transmitted to third-parties which specialize in routinely providing such information. 

As a general rule, we maintain the above information as a means of communicating with you, marketing to you and improving the interactive experience of our Web sites. For example, we may sometimes use the above information to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, or to contact you about your account with us. 

Periodically, we may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our sites, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, or to assist us in statistical analysis. 

**We do not report to any government, or other entity, customer balances or transactions that are placed in accounts. It is the customers responsibility to report any wins or losses if applicable in their country. We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information in response to a court order or a subpoena or in response to a law enforcement agency's request.**

 **No Minors, Please!**  
Our Web sites and their material are not suitable for minors, nor, obviously, are they directed to persons below the age of 21. We do not permit, and wherever possible, we actively seek to prevent or dissuade registration from persons below these ages. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from persons under 21 years of age.

 **Third-Party Sites Which Collect Information**  
Some of our Web sites may contain links to other sites whose information practices may differ from ours. In some cases, we have entered into agreements with these other sites or companies in order to allow them to bring you the services you may find displayed on our sites. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. As a general rule, we maintain no control over these third parties' use of this information. Visitors and Members should consult the other sites' privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

 **Cookies. . .**  
We use "cookies" to enhance your experience with our sites and to enable us to market to you products, services and other Web sites which we think you will find to be of interest. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, becoming a registered Member at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

Cookies help us to determine if you are a repeat visitor, determine the number of page views and entry points to our sites and in some cases, help us to gauge the overall flow and design of our Web sites to aid you and other visitors in your future enjoyment. 

Should you prefer not to permit the collection of information through the use of cookies, many browsers offer preferences allowing users to accept and reject cookies. 

**Our Commitment to Security**  
We take reasonable precautions when it comes to providing the proper levels of physical, electronic, and managerial support to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and to correctly use the information we collect online.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

* unauthorised access
* improper use or disclosure
* unauthorised modification
* unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

Although we take what we consider appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

 **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any specific questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or if you believe we have obtained certain data about you which you believe is erroneous, you may make any inquiries or send any corrections by writing to us at:

Attn.: Privacy Policy  
BETJAMAICA LTD.  
#1 Mangrove Way  
MBFZ Freeport  
Montego Bay, Jamaica

We reserve the right to seek verification of your identity before giving out information.
